Guide to the UE Publications Collection, 1936-1990s UE.8.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- The 8th International Convention Proceedings, September 1942 (Box 14, Volume 4)
- The 9th International Convention Proceedings, September 1943 (Box 14, Volume 5)
- The 10th International Convention Proceedings, September 1944 (Box 14, Volume 6)
- The 11th International Convention Proceedings, September 1946 (Box 14, Volume 7)
- The 12th International Convention Proceedings, September 1947 (Box 14, Volume 8)
- The 13th International Convention Proceedings, September 1948 (Box 14, Volume 9)
- The 14th International Convention Proceedings, September 1949 (Box 14, Volume 10)
- The 15th International Convention Proceedings, September 1950 (Box 14, Volume 11)
- The 16th International Convention Proceedings, September 1951 (Box 14, Volume 12)
- The 17th International Convention Proceedings, September 1952 (Box 14, Volume 13)
- The 18th International Convention Proceedings, September 1953 (Box 14, Volume 14)
- The 19th International Convention Proceedings, September 1954 (Box 14, Volume 15)
- The 20th International Convention Proceedings, September 1955 (Box 14, Volume 16)
- The 21st International Convention Proceedings, September 1956 (Box 14, Volume 17)
- The 22nd International Convention Proceedings, August 1957 (Box 14, Volume 18)
- The 23rd International Convention Proceedings, September 1958 (Box 14, Volume 19)
- The 24th International Convention Proceedings, September 1959 (Box 14, Volume 20)
- The 25th International Convention Proceedings, September 1960 (Box 14, Volume 21)
- The 26th International Convention Proceedings, September 1961 (Box 14, Volume 22)
- The 27th International Convention Proceedings, August 1962 (Box 15, Volume 23)
- The 28th International Convention Proceedings, September 1963 (Box 15, Volume 24)
- The 29th International Convention Proceedings, September 1964 (Box 15, Volume 25)
- The 30th International Convention Proceedings, September 1965 (Box 15, Volume 26)
- The 31st International Convention Proceedings, June 1966 (Box 15, Volume 27)
- The 32nd International Convention Proceedings, August 1967 (Box 15, Volume 28)
- The 33rd International Convention Proceedings, September 1968 (Box 15, Volume 29)
- The 34th International Convention Proceedings, September 1969 (Box 15, Volume 30)
- The 35th International Convention Proceedings with General Officers Report and Policy, September 1970 (Box 15, Volume 31)
- The 36th International Convention Proceedings with General Officers Report and Policy, August 1971 (Box 15, Volume 32)
- The 37th International Convention Proceedings, September 1972 (Box 15, Volume 33)
- The 38th International Convention Proceedings, September 1973 (Box 15, Volume 34)
- The 39th International Convention Proceedings, September 1974 (Box 15, Volume 35)
- The 40th International Convention Proceedings, September 1975 (Box 15, Volume 36)
- The 41st International Convention Proceedings, September 1976 (Box 15, Volume 37)
- The 42nd International Convention Proceedings, September 1977 (Box 15, Volume 38)
- The 43rd International Convention Proceedings, September 1978 (Box 15, Volume 39)
- The 44th International Convention Proceedings with General Officers Report and Policy, September 1979 (Box 15, Volume 40)
- The 46th International Convention Proceedings, September 1981 (Box 15, Volume 41)
- The 49th International Convention Proceedings, September 1984 (Box 15, Volume 42)
- The 50th International Convention Proceedings, September 1985 (Box 15, Volume 43)
- The 51st International Convention Proceedings, September 1986 (Box 15, Volume 44)
- The 52nd International Convention Proceedings, August 1987 (Box 15, Volume 45)
- The 53rd International Convention Proceedings, August 1988 (Box 16, Volume 46)
- The 54th International Convention Proceedings, August 1989 (Box 16, Volume 47)
- The 55th International Convention Proceedings, August 1990 (Box 16, Volume 48)
- The 56th International Convention Proceedings, August 1991 (Box 16, Volume 49)
- Support UE Workers in Their Fight for a Living Wage!, February 1, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 838)
- Local 107 Stewards Guide, May 1954 (Box 16, Folder 839)
- Strike Benefits Remarks of Secretary-Treasurer Matles at the 33rd UE Convention, September 1968 (Box 16, Folder 840)
- James Matles In Memoriam, September 27, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 841)
- Report of the CIO Delegation to the Soviet Union (Box 16, Folder 842)